vizu.com 2013-06-29

# Privacy Policy

**We take user privacy extremely seriously.**

Where necessary, a detailed privacy policy for your country is available below if you wish to review the complete legalese. This is such an important topic however that we have put together below a set of summary questions and answers that we frequently hear and respond to ourselves. We hope that after reading these questions you will clearly understand what we do and the value that we provide to the Internet ecosystem. 

**What does Vizu do?**

We provide research services to advertisers and marketers so that they understand how well (or not) their online advertising campaigns are working. Our information is used for understanding advertising performance only, and is not used to target ads to consumers. 

You may have reached this page by clicking on a privacy policy link from one of our surveys running across the Internet or on a mobile device. This survey unit is how we collect our data, by surveying actual users on the Internet as they are being exposed to online advertising. 

**What information about me does Vizu collect?**

As you surf websites on the Internet and access applications on mobile devices, you are exposed to advertising that is the primary source of revenue for those sites. We provide a technology that is used with these ads to understand if they are affecting opinions. When you are exposed to one of these ads Vizu collects some anonymous information related to your exposure history (e.g., how many individual ads in each campaign you were exposed to, how many times you saw each one, which site you were on when you saw each advertisement, and your survey response if you answered). This data is used to measure the impact the campaign is having on users. 

The information that we collect is strictly limited to the ad campaign data described above. We never know who you are and we would not have the ability to identify you or tie any survey response back to you. 

**How will the information Vizu collects about me be used?**

Vizu provides aggregated report data about various audiences that were exposed to advertising campaigns. This information is provided to the advertisers and marketers responsible for those campaigns, and aids them in improving their advertising efforts in the future. These advertisers spend money on the websites and applications that you view freely across the Internet, and Vizu is a critical part of enabling and improving this ecosystem. 

Vizu does not provide user level data to enable ad retargeting or other purposes related to identifying a specific person. And it is important to remember that Vizu never knows who you are; all data collection is completely anonymous and cannot be tied back to you. 

**Why is this important? Why should I be ok with Vizu tracking me?**

The vast majority of the sites and applications on the Internet are free for users, and are able to survive as businesses because of the revenue they generate from advertising campaigns that run on their properties. Advertising essentially pays for much of the content and functionality on the Internet that you use every day. 

Vizu plays an important role in this ecosystem by providing a safe and anonymous measurement system so that advertisers know exactly what is and is not effective about their ad campaigns. This keeps advertising revenue flowing to the media properties you frequent, and keeps your viewing experience largely free of charge. We have strived to provide a meaningful service for advertisers with valuable data they can use, and that also respects your user privacy. If you encounter Vizu's technology you should be aware that our advertising customers will never know any information about you specifically that they could use to contact you in the future, and Vizu will not use your responses to retarget advertising to you. 

**Can I opt out of Vizu collecting any information about me?**

You can opt out of in-browser tracking, by clicking the button below. This will download an "opt-out" cookie onto your computer which will prevent any future data collection on your computer. As long as this opt-out cookie remains on your computer Vizu will not collect any data about you on your computer. To opt out of tracking on your mobile device, you can update the setting on the device itself to limit ad tracking. 

  * Click here to view the privacy policy for the United States and Australia.
  * Click here to view the privacy policy for the United Kingdom.

**Last Updated: 22 February 2013**

Vizu Corporation ("Vizu," "we," or "us"), located at 185 Berry Street Suite 5200, San Francisco, California 94107, USA, is a member of the Nielsen family of companies ("Nielsen"). We recognize the importance of protecting the privacy rights of our users and we have created this Privacy Policy to explain our privacy practices so you will understand when and how information is collected, used, disclosed and protected through our Ad Catalyst service located at the primary Internet domain of Vizu.com (the "Site"). By accessing our Site or services, or responding to any survey through the services, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. 

**What does Vizu do?**

Vizu provides a survey research and measurement service that monitors the performance of brand advertising campaigns on the Internet and in ad-supported mobile applications to help advertisers and marketers understand how effectively their digital advertising campaigns perform. 

**How Vizu Uses Cookies and Unique Identifiers**

We use cookies at the Site, [www.vizu.com](http://www.vizu.com/), and in the Internet version of our Ad Catalyst measurement service. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, or to provide information to the owners of the site as well as doing web analytics, which means statistical market research services. In the version of Ad Catalyst that works in ad-supported mobile applications (the “in-app” version), we use a hashed version of a mobile device’s identifier instead of a cookie. Hashing makes the device’s identifier anonymous while keeping it unique. 

_At Vizu.com_

We use two kinds of cookies at our Site. The Google Analytics cookie collects information about how visitors use our Site, which we use to help improve it. Among other things, the cookies collect information about the number of visitors to the Site, where visitors have come to the Site from and the pages they visit while they are here. The Google Analytics cookie remains on your computer after you close your browser; this type of cookie is known as a "persistent" cookie. We use another persistent cookie when Vizu clients log in to the Ad Catalyst dashboard through the Site. This cookie keeps track of when Vizu clients log into the dashboard. 

_In Internet Ad Catalyst_

Ad Catalyst is a web analytics service that uses a cookie with a unique identifier to record whether an advertisement was displayed to a particular browser and whether a person using that browser answered a survey about that particular advertising campaign. The information collected using these cookies is limited to a list of the advertising creative units in the campaigns that were displayed to the computer, the sites on which the advertisements appeared, along with the number of times each unit was shown and the day/time of each exposure. 

If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies on the Internet, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to decline the use of cookies. Some features of the service, including opting out, may not work properly if you decline the use of cookies. To learn more about cookies, please visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>. For more information about how to opt-out of our services, see the section entitled "Opting Out" below. To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. 

_In "In-App" Ad Catalyst_

In the mobile in-app environment, Ad Catalyst uses a hashed version of a mobile device’s ID as an anonymous unique identifier to record whether an advertisement was displayed on a particular mobile device. The information collected using these unique identifiers is limited to a list of the advertising creative units in the campaigns that were displayed on the device, the apps in which the advertisements appeared, along with the number of times each ad unit was shown and the day/time of each exposure. 

If you do not want your in-app ad exposure measured, or you would like to clear your tracking history, you can adjust the settings on your mobile device. On an iOS 6 device, go to the device’s Settings menu, and change the setting to limit ad tracking. To reset your tracking on Android mobile devices, go to the Settings menu and reset your device to its original factory settings. 

**How Vizu's survey research and measurement service works**

Advertisers include a Vizu tag with their ads and then place the ads on select sites around the web and in select mobile applications. The information collected includes the number of impressions each ad receives, how many individual ads in each campaign each Internet browser session or mobile device was exposed to, how many times each ad was displayed, and which site the viewer was on or which ad-supported mobile application was running when the the ad was displayed. No personal data are collected from viewers of advertisements or from their mobile devices, and the IP address of a viewer’s computer, mobile or other device is not collected or stored. 

The service also presents a single survey question randomly to a small subset of the viewers of an advertising campaign. This question is a multiple choice question with a predetermined set of answer choices related to the primary marketing objective of the ad campaign. Responses are voluntary. If the viewer responds to a survey question, the response is stored in a database. The surveys do not ask for or collect any personal data; all survey responses are anonymous and are **_not_** linked to the Vizu cookie. 

The anonymous information is aggregated, analyzed and reported to the advertisers and marketers managing the advertising campaigns. 

By responding to a survey, you consent to the collection and use of the information as described in this policy. 

**What information do we collect?**

_The Vizu service does not collect, record or store personally identifiable information and does not collect or store IP Addresses._

"Personally identifiable information" is information that identifies you as an individual, such as your name, mobile phone number or email address. The Vizu service does not collect any personally identifiable information of viewers and survey respondents. 

Your "IP address" is a number that is automatically assigned by your Internet service provider (ISP) to the computer, mobile or other device that you use when you access the Internet. The Vizu service does not collect or store the IP address of your computer, mobile or other device. 

"Non-personally identifiable information" is any information that does not reveal your specific identity, such as browser information, behavioral data collected through cookies, pixel tags and other technologies, demographic information, and aggregated information. 

_From Customers_

For Vizu customers who are using the service to measure their advertising efforts, registration is required to enable access to some features, functionality, and information on the Site, to send them specific information related to their service, to allow them to access stored information, and to facilitate communication from Vizu. When registering on Vizu.com, customers may need to provide their full name and email address. Customers must also select a username and password for their account. 

_From Internet Viewers_

Vizu records how many times a Vizu-tagged advertisement was displayed to a browser that has a Vizu cookie ("viewer"), how many different ads in a particular campaign were displayed to a viewer, and on which websites the advertisements were seen. This information is used to understand what impact the campaign is having on users. 

_From Mobile Application Viewers_

Vizu can record how many times a Vizu-tagged advertisement was displayed on a mobile device (“viewer”), how many different ads in a particular campaign were displayed to a viewer, and on which ad-supported mobile applications the advertisements were seen. This information is used to understand what impact the campaign is having on users. 

_From Internet Survey Respondents_

As mentioned before, the Vizu service presents a single survey question to a small subset of the viewers of an Internet advertising campaign. Responses are entirely voluntary. 

Vizu records whether a survey relating to a Vizu-tagged advertising campaign was presented to particular browser with a stored Vizu cookie and whether the viewer answered the survey question. Vizu also records the respondent’s answer to the survey question but does not link the survey answers to the Vizu Ad Catalyst cookie. Surveys do not ask for or collect any personally-identifiable information. The information that we collect is non-personally identifiable and strictly limited to the ad campaign data described above. 

_From Mobile Application Survey Respondents_

The Vizu service presents a single survey question to a small subset of the viewers of an in-app mobile advertising campaign. Responses are entirely voluntary. 

Vizu records whether the viewer answered the survey question. Vizu also records the respondent’s answer to the survey question. Surveys do not ask for or collect any personally-identifiable information. The information that we collect is non-personally identifiable and strictly limited to the ad campaign data described above. 

By responding to a Vizu Internet or mobile application survey and providing such information, you consent to the collection and use of the information as described in this policy. 

**How do we use this information?**

Vizu uses the data that it collects to provide its services to its customers and viewers. Vizu aggregates the non-personally identifiable data and provides those data to the advertisers and marketers responsible for the advertising campaigns. The anonymous data collected by the Vizu service is reported to our customers in an aggregated, summarized format, and our customers may use the data to learn how advertising campaigns performed, including which ad units were most effective, and can be improved for the future. Vizu may also use the data internally to improve and enhance its services. 

Vizu does not provide user level data to aid in ad retargeting or other purposes related to contacting a specific person. 

**With whom do we share information?**

Vizu provides the data and reports to its customer advertisers and marketers responsible for the advertising campaigns as described above in the "How do we use this information?" section. 

We may employ or contract with other companies or individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. Such companies or individuals may be provided with access to your information only if needed to perform their functions, and are prohibited from using such information for any other purpose. In the event of a change in ownership, merger or acquisition with another entity, sale or transfer of company assets, or in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership, we reserve the right to transfer all of Vizu's customer, viewer and survey respondent information, including the personally identifiable information of our customers, to third parties as one of our business assets. 

Vizu may disclose collected information pursuant to a subpoena or other judicial or administrative order, where required by law, or, at our sole discretion, where we deem it necessary to protect the safety of any individual or the public, preserve our legal rights, take action regarding potentially illegal activities, or to prevent the violation of our Terms of Service Agreement or of the rights of Vizu or any third party. 

**How do we protect your information?**

We store the information described in this Privacy Policy for as long as needed for the market research purposes as described in this Policy. We have implemented certain commercially reasonable organizational, technical and administrative security measures designed to help protect the security and confidentiality of information while controlled by us. We limit access to information to employees and agents who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information, all of whom are bound by this Privacy Policy. Access or use of information for any purpose other than those explained in this Privacy Policy will not be authorized. 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We strongly recommend that you employ a secure browser - one that supports secure transmission of data across the Internet. For more information, consult your browser's help feature. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of any account you might have with us has been compromised), please immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us as set forth below. 

Please note, if you are a customer and do not logout once registered for services that require registration, your information could be viewed by other users with access to your computer. Your Vizu password is protected so that only you can access it and view the member information relevant to the account. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Vizu will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or email. Ultimately, you are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information. 

**Opting Out**

Viewers of Internet ad campaigns are free to opt-out of measurement by the Vizu service at any time. An opt-out button to accomplish this is provided at the bottom of this page. This will download an "opt-out" or "do-not-track" cookie onto your computer and you will no longer be tracked or surveyed by Vizu about ad campaigns that you may view. As long as this opt-out cookie remains on your computer Vizu will not collect any data about you. You must keep this do-not-track cookie on your computer and not remove it in order to remain opt-ed out of the collection of information through the Vizu service. If your machine automatically removes cookies or you remove the opt-out cookie periodically, you will have to opt out again. 

Viewers of ad campaigns that appear within mobile applications can opt out of tracking advertising exposure on an iOS 6 device by changing the setting to limit ad tracking in the Settings menu of the device. To reset your tracking on Android mobile devices, in the Settings menu, reset your device to original factory settings. 

_To opt-out please click the button above._

##  Children Under 13 

Vizu's Site and service are not directed to children under the age of 13 and Vizu does not collect personally identifiable information from anyone, including children under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian believes that this Site has collected the personal information of a child under the age of 13 (for example, if a child has registered for an account), please contact Vizu at the address below and we will use our best efforts to remove the information from our records. 

**Updates to this Privacy Policy**

Vizu reserves the right to update and change this Privacy Policy. If we make any material changes to our Privacy Policy, we will post a new statement on our Site and update the "Last Updated" date at the top of the Privacy Policy. Therefore, we encourage you to check this Privacy Policy frequently to stay apprised of any updates and changes. Please take a look at the "Last Updated" legend at the top of this page to see when this Privacy Policy was last revised. Any changes to this Privacy Policy will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy on the Site. Your responses to Internet or mobile application surveys or use of the Site and service following these changes mean that you accept the revised Privacy Policy. 

**Third Party Privacy Policies**

This Privacy Policy does not address, and we are not responsible for, the privacy policies, information or other practices of any third parties, including any third party operating any site linked to our Site or to which this Site contains a link. The inclusion of a link on the Site does not imply endorsement of the linked site by us or by our affiliates. For more information about how our clients use the information collected on their websites, please see their privacy policies. 

**Who can I contact for more information?**

If you have any comments or questions you may contact us at <http://brandlift.vizu.com/about/contact/> or Vizu Corporation 185 Berry Street Suite 5200, San Francisco, California 94107, USA. 

**Last Updated: September 20, 2012**

Vizu Corporation ("Vizu," "we," or "us"), located at 185 Berry Street Suite 5200, San Francisco, California 94107, USA, is a member of the Nielsen family of companies ("Nielsen"). We recognize the importance of protecting the privacy rights of our users and we have created this Cookie and Privacy Policy to explain our privacy practices so you will understand when and how information is collected, used, disclosed and protected through our Ad Catalyst service and the Vizu.com website (the "Site"). By accessing our Site or services, or responding to any survey through the services, you agree to the terms and conditions of this Cookie and Privacy Policy. 

**What does Vizu do?**

Vizu provides a survey research and measurement service that monitors the performance of brand advertising campaigns on the Internet to help advertisers and marketers understand how effectively their online advertising campaigns perform. 

**How Vizu Uses Cookies**

We use cookies at the Site, [www.vizu.com](http://www.vizu.com/), and in our Ad Catalyst measurement service. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, or to provide information to the owners of the site as well as doing web analytics, which means statistical market research services. 

The table below explains the cookies we use and why. 

**Cookie**

| 

**Name**

| 

**Purpose**

| 

**More information**

| 

**Expiration date**  
  
---|---|---|---|---  
  
Ad Catalyst Dashboard 

| 

adcatalyst.vizu.com 

| 

This cookie is used to register activity when clients log-in to the Ad Catalyst service dashboard 

| 

Use browser controls 

Vizu opt-out cookie <http://www.vizu.com/w3c/policy.htm>

| 

2 years   
  
Ad Catalyst ad effectiveness cookie 

| 

vizu.com 

| 

This cookie is used to register whether a particular advertisement was displayed 

| 

Vizu opt-out cookie <http://www.vizu.com/w3c/policy.htm>

| 

2 years   
  
Survey cookie 

| 

vizu.com 

| 

This cookie is associated with the survey that is displayed 

| 

Vizu opt-out cookie <http://www.vizu.com/w3c/policy.htm>

| 

2 years   
  
Vizu website cookie 

| 

googleanalytics.com 

_utma 

_utmb 

_utmc 

_utmz 

| 

These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our Site, which we use to help improve it. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the Site from, and the pages they visit. 

| 

To withdraw your consent after accepting this cookie, delete the Google Analytics cookies. Find out how at [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/). 

To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. 

| 

2 years   
  
Most web browsers allow some control of most cookies through the browser settings. To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) or [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/). 

_At Vizu.com_

We use two kinds of cookies at our Site. The Google Analytics cookie collects information about how visitors use our Site, which we use to help improve it. Among other things, the cookies collect information about the number of visitors to the Site, where visitors have come to the Site from and the pages they visit while they are here. The Google Analytics cookie remains on your computer after you close your browser; this type of cookie is known as a "persistent" cookie. We use another persistent cookie when Vizu clients log in to the Ad Catalyst dashboard through the Site. This cookie keeps track of when Vizu clients log into the dashboard. 

_In Ad Catalyst_

Ad Catalyst is a web analytics service that uses a persistent cookie with a unique identifier to record whether an advertisement was displayed to a particular browser and whether a person using that browser answered a survey about that particular advertising campaign. The data collected using these cookies is limited to a list of the advertising creative units in the campaigns displayed to the computer containing the Vizu cookie, the sites on which the advertisements appeared, along with the number of times each unit was shown and the day/time of each exposure. 

If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to decline the use of cookies. Some features of the service, including opting out, may not work properly if you decline the use of cookies. To learn more about cookies, please visit <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/>. For more information about how to opt-out of our services, see the section entitled "Opting Out" below. To opt out of being tracked by Google Analytics across all websites visit <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. 

**How Vizu's survey research and measurement service works**

Advertisers include a Vizu tag with their ads and then place the ads on select sites around the web. The information collected includes the number of impressions each ad receives, how many individual ads in each campaign each viewer was exposed to, how many times a viewer saw each ad, and which site the viewer was on when the viewer saw the ad. No personal data are collected from viewers of advertisements and the IP address of a viewer's computer, mobile or other device is not collected, recorded or stored. 

The service also presents a single survey question randomly to a small subset of the viewers of an advertising campaign. This question is a multiple choice question with a predetermined set of answer choices related to the primary marketing objective of the ad campaign. Responses are voluntary. If the viewer responds to a survey question, the response is stored in a database. The surveys do not ask for or collect any personal data; all survey responses are anonymous and are **_not_** linked to the Vizu cookie. 

The anonymous information is aggregated, analyzed and reported to the advertisers and marketers managing the advertising campaigns. 

By responding to a survey, you consent to the collection and use of the information as described in this policy. 

**What information do we collect?**

_The Vizu service does not collect, or record or store personal data like name or email address and does not collect or store IP Addresses._

_From Customers_

For Vizu customers who are using the service to measure the effectiveness of their advertising efforts, registration is required to enable access to some features, functionality, and information on the Site, to send customers specific information related to their service, to allow them to access stored information, and to facilitate communication from Vizu. When registering on Vizu, customers may need to provide their full name and email address. Customers must also select a username and password for their account. 

_From Viewers_

Vizu records how many times a Vizu-tagged advertisement was displayed to a browser with a Vizu cookie ("viewer"), how many different ads in a particular campaign were displayed to a viewer, and on which websites the advertisements were seen. 

_From Survey Respondents_

Vizu records whether a survey relating to a Vizu-tagged advertising campaign was presented to particular browser with a Vizu cookie and whether the viewer answered the survey question. Vizu also records the respondent's answer to the survey question but does _not_ associate the survey answers to the Vizu Ad Catalyst cookie. 

**How do we use this information?**

Vizu uses the data that it collects to provide its services to its customers and viewers. Vizu aggregates the anonymous data and provides those data to the advertisers and marketers responsible for the advertising campaigns. The anonymous data collected by the Vizu service is reported to our customers in an aggregated, summarized format, and our customers may use the data to learn how advertising campaigns performed, including which ad units were most effective, and how their campaigns can be improved for the future. Vizu may also use the data internally to improve and enhance its services. 

Vizu does not provide user level data to aid in ad retargeting or other purposes related to contacting a specific person. 

**With whom do we share information?**

Vizu provides the data and reports to its customer advertisers and marketers responsible for the advertising campaigns as described above in the "How do we use this information?" section. 

In the event of a change in ownership, merger or acquisition with another entity, sale or transfer of company assets, or in the event of an insolvency, bankruptcy or receivership, we reserve the right to transfer all of Vizu's information, including personal data of its customers, to third parties as part of our business assets. 

Vizu may disclose collected information pursuant to a subpoena or other judicial or administrative order, where required by law, or, at our sole discretion, where we deem it necessary to protect the safety of any individual or the public, preserve our legal rights, take action regarding potentially illegal activities, or to prevent the violation of our Terms of Service Agreement or of the rights of Vizu or any third party. 

**How do we protect your information?**

We store the information described in this Cookie and Privacy Policy for only as long as needed for the market research purposes as described in this Cookie and Privacy Policy. We have implemented certain commercially reasonable organisational, technical and administrative security measures designed to help protect the security and confidentiality of information while controlled by us. We limit access to the information collected through our services to employees and agents who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information, all of whom are bound by this Cookie and Privacy Policy. Access or use of information for any purpose other than those explained in this Cookie and Privacy Policy will not be authorized. 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. We strongly recommend that you regularly employ a secure browser \- one that supports secure transmission of data across the Internet. For more information, consult your browser's help feature. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of any account you might have with us has been compromised), please immediately notify us of the problem by contacting us as set forth below. 

Please note, if you are a customer and do not logout once registered for services that require registration, your information could be viewed by other users with access to your computer. Your Vizu password is protected so that only you can access it and view the member information relevant to the account. We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. Vizu will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or email. Ultimately, you are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and any account information. 

**Opting Out**

Viewers of ad campaigns are free to opt-out of measurement by the Vizu service at any time. An opt-out button to accomplish this is provided at the bottom of this page. This will download an "opt-out" or "do-not-track" cookie onto your machine and you will no longer be tracked or surveyed about ad campaigns that you may view. As long as this opt-out cookie remains on your computer, Vizu will not collect any data about you. You must keep this do-not-track cookie on your computer and not remove it in order to remain opt-ed out of the collection of information through the Vizu service. If your machine automatically removes cookies or you remove the opt-out cookie periodically, you will have to opt out again. 

_To opt-out please click the button above._

**Updates to this Cookie and Privacy Policy**

Vizu reserves the right to update and change this Cookie and Privacy Policy. If we make any material changes to our Cookie and Privacy Policy, we will post a new statement on our Site and update the "Last Updated" date set forth above. Therefore, we encourage you to check this Cookie and Privacy Policy frequently to stay apprised of any updates and changes. Please take a look at the "Last Updated" legend at the top of this page to see when this Cookie and Privacy Policy was last revised. Any changes to this Cookie and Privacy Policy will become effective when we post the revised Cookie and Privacy Policy on the Site. Your responses to surveys or use of the Site and service after these changes become effective mean that you accept the revised Cookie and Privacy Policy. 

**Third Party Privacy Policies**

This Cookie and Privacy Policy does not address, and we are not responsible for, the privacy, information or other practices of any third parties, including any third party operating any site linked to our Site or to which this Site contains a link. The inclusion of a link on the Site does not imply endorsement of the linked site by us or by our affiliates. For more information about how our clients use the information collected on their websites, please see their privacy policies. 

**Who can I contact for more information?**

If you have any comments or questions you may contact us at <http://brandlift.vizu.com/about/contact/> or Vizu Corporation, 185 Berry Street, Suite 5200, San Francisco, California 94107, USA, or c/o Nielsen NetRatings UK Limited, at AC Nielsen House, London Road, Headington OX3 9RX, United Kingdom.
